Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 470, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Summary of the Health Security Act, 1994; Publication (Box 470, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 471, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Spotlight on Health and Safety., 1975; Publication (Box 471, Folder 1)
    Author: Industrial Union Dept.
    Notes: v.4:no.2-4 (1975)
  - Item 2: Spotlight on Health and Safety., 1976; Publication (Box 471, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.1-3 (1976)
  - Item 3: Spotlight on Health and Safety., 1977; Publication (Box 471, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.1-2, 4 (1977)
  - Item 4: Spotlight on Health and Safety., 1978; Publication (Box 471, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.7:no.1-4 (1978)
  - Item 5: Spotlight on Health and Safety., 1979; Publication (Box 471, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.1-2 (1979)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 471, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Constitution., 1988; Publication (Box 471, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Constitution., 1992; Publication (Box 471, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Job Training Update., 1987; Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
    Author: Human Resource Development Institute
    Notes: v.1:no.8 (1987)
  - Item 2: Job Training Update., 1988; Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.1-7, 9, 11 (1988)
  - Item 3: Job Training Update., 1989; Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.1-2, 5 (1989)
  - Item 4: Job Training Update., 1991; Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.5:no.6 (1991)
  - Item 5: Job Training Update., 1992; Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
    Notes: Jan/Feb (1992)
  - Item 6: Accountability., 1992; Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
    Notes: Issue 6, 9 (1992)
  - Item 7: HRDI Job Training Update., 1993; Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
    Notes: Jan/Feb, Nov/Dec (1993)
  - Item 8: HRDI Job Training Update., 1994; Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
    Notes: Mar/Apr (1994)
  - Item 9: HRDI Job Training Update., 1995; Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
    Notes: May/June (1995)
  - Item 10: HRDI Advisory, 1993; Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.1 (1993)
  - Item 11: HRDI Advisory, 1994; Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.5 (1994)
  - Item 12: HRDI Advisory, 1995; Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.3 (1995)
  - Item 13: Surviving layoffs, Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Coping with a closing, Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: How to form a Joint Training Program, Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: The American Workforce in transition, 1995; Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: "In recognition of the AFL-CIO Human Resources Dev. Institutes, expertise", 1996; Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: "I am writing to urge your review and comment on the enclosed federal regulations governing", 1988; Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: AFL-CIO comments on proposed regulations governing Title III of the job training partnership act, 1988; Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: Federal Register., 1988; Publication (Box 471, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.53:no.205 (1988)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 471, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Handbook for labor representatives serving on private industry councils under the Job Training Partnership Act, 1984; Publication (Box 471, Folder 4)
    Author: Human Resources Development Institute
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 471, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A short history of American Labor, Publication (Box 471, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: One hundred years of American labor, 1881-1981, Publication (Box 471, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 471, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Working together ... the key to jobs for workers with disabilities: an AFL/CIO guide, Publication (Box 471, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Union perspectives on new work-based youth apprenticeship initiatives, 1992; Publication (Box 471, Folder 6)
    Author: Carol Shenon
    Notes: Researched and written by Carol Shenon for the Human Resources Development Institute
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 471, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Health care reform: training program manual, 1994; Publication (Box 471, Folder 7)
    Author: Dept. of Education; The George Meany Center for Labor Studies
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 471, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Conference packets. National Health Care / Now is the time, 1990; Publication (Box 471, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: National Health Care Reform: Launching the corporate campaign, Publication (Box 471, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: National Health Care Reform: Organizing in your community, Publication (Box 471, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: National Health Care Reform: Working at the bargaining table, Publication (Box 471, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 471, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1970; Publication (Box 471, Folder 9)
    Author: Government Employes Council
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 471, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Can your children afford to earn less this summer?, Publication (Box 471, Folder 10)
    Author: Frontlash
  - Item 2: Some politicians want you to earn less. Could you afford it?, Publication (Box 471, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 471, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: National Health Care Reform: Launching the corporate campaign, Publication (Box 471, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: National Health Care Reform: Organizing in your community, Publication (Box 471, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Fact Sheet - The Clinton reform proposal: Quality, Publication (Box 471, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Fact Sheet - The Clinton reform proposal: Cost Containment & Financing, Publication (Box 471, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Fact Sheet - The Clinton reform proposal: Benefits, Publication (Box 471, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 471, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Testimony of Eugenia Kemblebefore the Commerce, State, Justice Subcommittee of the House Appropriations Committee, 1986; Publication (Box 471, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Statement of Eugenia Kembleto the International Operations Subcommittee of the House Foreign Affairs Committee, 1986; Publication (Box 471, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: RTW 14 (b), anything but, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
    Author: Task Force on Labor Law Reform
  - Item 2: The Fight for labor law reform, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Small business has been sold a bill of goods.., Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: An important law of this land is being flagrantly violated, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Now it's time to balance the scales, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: The Workers' law, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Where it stands, what's in labor law reform bill after Senate Committee Action, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: News from American Justice on the Job. for release. Americans for Justice on the job, criticizes U.S. News & World Report's refusal to carry advertisement supporing labor law reform, 1978; Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Justice on the job, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: The big lie campaign against hatch act reform, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: AFL-CIO News. vol. XXIII, no. 19 (1978), Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Georgia Businessman tells why labor law reform is needed, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Some of your best friendsguilty?, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Americans united for labor law reform, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Brief synopsis of labor law reform, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Labor law reform is halway home., Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Labor law reform - why it is needed, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: the Justification for reform - Lawlessness becoming the rule, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Union Security in America, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
    Author: Daniel H. Pollitt
  - Item 20: From coast to Coastmajor newspaapers back the labor law reform bill because 'it's not fair', Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: Members of Congress speak out: nine cases that show 'jusice delayed is justice denied', Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: As 1978 comes along We're half-way home on labor law reform, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: Honesty in bargaining, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
    Author: Benjamin M. Shieber
  - Item 24: Here's what we face!, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: Minimum wage - still fighting the war on poverty, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
    Author: Gus Tyler
  - Item 26: The moral case against right - to - work, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 27: The truth about newspaper endorsements of Labor Law Reform (booklet of articles), Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: National Journal. Labor law reform: a consumer concern, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 29: National Journal. Labor law reform: a black perspective, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 30: National Journal. a safe landing for labor law reform?, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 31: National Journal. Labor law reform: what it would really accomplish, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - Item 32: What labor law must overcome, Publication (Box 472, Folder 1)
- Labor Institute of Public Affairs, Publication (Box 472, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Programs and resources from LIPA, 1986; Publication (Box 472, Folder 2)
    Author: Labor Institute of Public Affairs
  - Item 2: News fromTwo labor specials set on PBS for week following Labor Day, 1986; Publication (Box 472, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: The AFL-CIO Labor Insitute of Public Affairs has produced a new one-hour program for public televisions this fall., 1995; Publication (Box 472, Folder 2)
    Notes: Correspondence. 2 copy
  - Item 4: Resource catalog: video, audio, print, advertising and promotional materials, 1995; Publication (Box 472, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Union produced videos, 1995; Publication (Box 472, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: article - AFL-CIO Twenty First Biennial Convention: taking labor into the 21st century, 1995; Publication (Box 472, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: catalog - Once it took a great set of lungs to get the message out, Publication (Box 472, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Abolish effective collective bargaining?, Publication (Box 472, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: You can usually tell a bill (labor law reform) by the company it keeps, 1978; Publication (Box 472, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 472, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: George Meany: His life works would do honor to a dozen men, Publication (Box 472, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Taming the economic jungle: a world safe for human values, 1990; Publication (Box 472, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Trade unionists & the hometown media, Publication (Box 472, Folder 3)
    Author: Dept. of Information
  - Item 4: Collective bargaining: democracy on the job., 1985; Publication (Box 472, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Jobs for the future: an AFL-CIO view, 1987; Publication (Box 472, Folder 3)
    Author: Thomas R. Donahue
  - Item 6: Why unions?, 1982; Publication (Box 472, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: This is the AFL-CIO, 1984; Publication (Box 472, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 472, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: ILCA editor's guide, Publication (Box 472, Folder 4)
    Author: International Labor Communications Assoc.
  - Item 2: The Bulletin - October 1990, Publication (Box 472, Folder 4)
    Author: Dept. of International Affairs
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 472, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Protecting the lives of workers is our highest priority, Publication (Box 472, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Action, 1992; Publication (Box 472, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.14:no.10 (1992)
  - Item 3: Action, 1993; Publication (Box 472, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.1:no.3 (1993)
  - Item 4: Developing new tactics: winning with coordinated corporate campaigns, 1985; Publication (Box 472, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Officers Report, 1982; Publication (Box 472, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Officers Report, 1984; Publication (Box 472, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Software & hardhats: technology and workers in the 21st century, 1992; Publication (Box 472, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Toxic crisis: time for action, 1985; Publication (Box 472, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Crossroads for American industry, 1986; Publication (Box 472, Folder 5)
    Author: Douglas A. Fraser
  - Item 10: The costs of aggression, 1992; Publication (Box 472, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Slow growth: no growth for inflation, 1978; Publication (Box 472, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 472, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: News release - Labor Day statement of Howard D. Samuel, 1981; Publication (Box 472, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Industrial Policy Brieging Book, 1982; Publication (Box 472, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 472, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Jobs with Justice - Photo slick, News article, and order form, 1988; Publication (Box 472, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Jobs with Justice - Folder of correspondence examples, Publication (Box 472, Folder 7)
- George Meany Center for Labor Studies, Publication (Box 473, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Catalogue., 1989-1990 (Box 473, Folder 1)
    Author: George Meany Center for Labor Studies
  - Item 2: Catalogue., 1990-1991 (Box 473, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Catalogue., 1992-1993 (Box 473, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Catalogue., 1994-1995 (Box 473, Folder 1)
- George Meany Center for Labor Studies, Publication (Box 473, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Catalogue., 1984-1985 (Box 473, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Catalogue., 1985-1986 (Box 473, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Catalogue., 1986-1987 (Box 473, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Catalogue., 1987-1988 (Box 473, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Catalogue., 1988-1989 (Box 473, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Seminar for Secretary-Treasurers --Background reading material, 1988; Publication (Box 473, Folder 2)
- George Meany Center for Labor Studies, Publication (Box 473, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Catalogue., 1977-1978 (Box 473, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Catalogue., 1978-1979 (Box 473, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Catalogue., 1979-1980 (Box 473, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Catalogue., 1980-1981 (Box 473, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Catalogue., 1981-1982 (Box 473, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Catalogue., 1982-1983 (Box 473, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Catalogue., 1983-1984 (Box 473, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 473, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: "As you are probably aware, the United States Senate is expected to take up S. 2467, the Labor Law Reform Bill, some time in March or early April", 1978; Publication (Box 473, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Statement byon Labor law reform, 1977; Publication (Box 473, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Sample editorial for Radio and Television, Publication (Box 473, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Sample letters to Senators on Hatch Act Reform, Publication (Box 473, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Sample petitions, Publication (Box 473, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: The truth about "right to work" laws: facts vs. propaganda, 1977; Publication (Box 473, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 473, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: President Carter's Message to Congress, Publication (Box 473, Folder 5)
    Notes: Special Reports
  - Item 2: Prominent Americans call for Labor Law Reform, Publication (Box 473, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Right to work, Publication (Box 473, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Rollcall Votes, Publication (Box 473, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Startling results of PIOR's new national poll, Publication (Box 473, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: The polls agree, Publication (Box 473, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: The Problem is the case load, Publication (Box 473, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: The Right Wing, Publication (Box 473, Folder 5)
    Notes: Special Reports. 2 copies
  - Item 9: The Union busters, Publication (Box 473, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: The Voices of Labor Law Reform, Publication (Box 473, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Cargo equity, Publication (Box 473, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: H.R. 8410 & S. 1883 Labor Law Reform, Publication (Box 473, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Labor Law Poll, Publication (Box 473, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: More voices of Labor Law Reform, Publication (Box 473, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Papers endorse S. 2467, Publication (Box 473, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 473, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Labor Law Reform, 1978; Publication (Box 473, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.2, no.15-17, 22-23, 25-26
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 473, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Sample Letters to Senators on Labor Law, S. 2467, Publication (Box 473, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Sample Letters to Congress, Publication (Box 473, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Sample Letters to Congress on 14(b) Repeal, Publication (Box 473, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Sample Letters to the Editor on 14(b) Repeal, Publication (Box 473, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Sample Letters to the Editor on Labor Law Reform, Publication (Box 473, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Sample Speeches on Labor Law Reform, Publication (Box 473, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Fact sheets on minimum wage, Publication (Box 473, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Labor and grass roots lobbying: a manual for Congressional District Coordinators, Publication (Box 473, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Speakers handbook on Labor Law Reform, Publication (Box 473, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Speakers handbook on Labor Law Reform: Book Two, Publication (Box 473, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 474, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: News - Transcripts of news conferences held by Lane Kirkland - 5/5/1987, 5/6/1987, Publication (Box 474, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: News - Transcripts of news conferences held by Lane Kirkland - 8/18/1987, 8/19/1987, Publication (Box 474, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: News - Transcripts of news conferences held by Lane Kirkland - 2/16-2/18/1987, Publication (Box 474, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: News - For use Tuesday, 2/26/1985, Publication (Box 474, Folder 1)
    Author: Department of Information
  - Item 5: News - For release 1983 Labor Day Weekend, Publication (Box 474, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: News - Transcripts of news conferences held by Lane Kirkland on 2/18-2/21/1985, Publication (Box 474, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: News - Transcripts of news conferences held by Lane Kirkland on 5/7-5/8/1984, Publication (Box 474, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: News - Transcripts of news conferences held by Lane Kirkland on 8/8-8/9/1983, Publication (Box 474, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: News - Transcripts of news conferences held by Lane Kirkland on 2/20-2/23/1984, Publication (Box 474, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: News - Transcripts of news conferences held by Lane Kirkland on 5/7-5/8/1985, Publication (Box 474, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: News - 1985 Labor Day message by Lane Kirkland, Publication (Box 474, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: News - Transcripts of news conferences held by Lane Kirkland on 8/13-8/14/1985, Publication (Box 474, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: News - ICFTU Report on violations of Trade Union Rights in China, 1989; Publication (Box 474, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: News - Transcripts of news conferences held by Lane Kirkland on 2/19-2/20/1990, Publication (Box 474, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 474, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The National Economy, 1979; Publication (Box 474, Folder 2)
    Notes: 2 copies.
  - Item 2: The National Economy, 1981; Publication (Box 474, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 474, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Planning your Meetings and Programs, Publication (Box 474, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 474, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Report of the President, 1980; Publication (Box 474, Folder 4)
    Author: Industrial Union Department
  - Item 2: Metaaletter, 1978; Publication (Box 474, Folder 4)
    Author: Metal Trades Department
    Notes: v.9:no.3 (1978)
  - Item 3: President's Report to the fifty-eighth convention, 1977; Publication (Box 474, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: What it is - What it does, Publication (Box 474, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 474, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Constitutions, 1981; Publication (Box 474, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Constitutions, 1985; Publication (Box 474, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 474, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Pacific Coast Master Agreement between the Pacific Coast shipbuilding and ship repair firms and the Metal Trades Department of the A.F.L-C.I.O. the Pacific Coast Metal Trades District Council the Local Metal Trades Council teh International Unions Signato, 1983; Publication (Box 474, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Pacific Coast Master Agreement between the Pacific Coast shipbuilding and ship repair firms and the Metal Trades Department of the A.F.L-C.I.O. the Pacific Coast Metal Trades District Council the Local Metal Trades Council teh International Unions Signato, 1980; Publication (Box 474, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Master agreement Pacific Coast Metal Trades District Council, San Francisco Bay Area, Service Engineering Co.: 1987-1988-1989, Publication (Box 474, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Agreement between the Ingalls Shipbuilding Division, Litton Systems, Inc., Pascagoula, Mississippi and the Metal Trades Department, AFL-CIO, Pascagoula Metal Trades Council: September 26, 1983-February 1, 1987, Publication (Box 474, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 474, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: George Meany: the making of a freedom fighter, 1979; Publication (Box 474, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: 85th birthday tribute to George Meany, 1979; Publication (Box 474, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 474, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: New technology in the workplace and its impact on the American worker, 1983; Publication (Box 474, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 474, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Constitution -, 1985; Publication (Box 474, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 474, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The People's lobby - 96th, 1981; Publication (Box 474, Folder 10)